<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Consultancy Servicess on Demonar Africa Solutions Ltd</title>
    <link>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Consultancy Servicess on Demonar Africa Solutions Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://demonar.netlify.app/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dissertation Guidance</title>
      <link>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/consultancy-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/consultancy-services/</guid>
      <description>We offer professional dissertation guidance at Masters and PhD level.
Basic Thesis and Dissertation Differences The main difference between a thesis and a dissertation is when they are completed. The thesis is a project that marks the end of a master&amp;rsquo;s program, while the dissertation occurs during doctoral study. The two are actually quite different in their purpose, as well. A thesis is a compilation of research that proves you are knowledgeable about the information learn throughout your graduate program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/research/</guid>
      <description>We are engaged in high level systematic investigation into and study of materials and sources in order to establish facts and reach new conclusions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construction Management</title>
      <link>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/construction-managemet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/construction-managemet/</guid>
      <description>The project is divided into several WBS(work breakdown structure) that are fully managed and coordinated by us. This option yields the client significant savings and flexibility with higher level of control on costs, time and quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project management</title>
      <link>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/project-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://demonar.netlify.app/services/project-management/</guid>
      <description>Depending upon the project requirement, we establish the procedure for the appointment of architect/engineer to produce the design and a main contractor to carry out the construction.
We set the strategy and manage the activities from pre-construction through completion and act as the single point of contract with the owner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
