<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Demonar Research</title>
    <link>www.example.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Demonar Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="www.example.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dissertation Guidance</title>
      <link>www.example.com/services/dissertation-guidance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/services/dissertation-guidance/</guid>
      <description>We offer professional dissertation guidance at Masters and PhD level.
Basic Thesis and Dissertation Differences The main difference between a thesis and a dissertation is when they are completed. The thesis is a project that marks the end of a master&amp;rsquo;s program, while the dissertation occurs during doctoral study. The two are actually quite different in their purpose, as well. A thesis is a compilation of research that proves you are knowledgeable about the information learn throughout your graduate program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>www.example.com/services/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/services/research/</guid>
      <description>We are engaged in high level systematic investigation into and study of materials and sources in order to establish facts and reach new conclusions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data analysis</title>
      <link>www.example.com/services/data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/services/data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>We deifine data analysis as a process of cleaning, transforming, and modeling data to discover useful information for business decision-making. The purpose of Data Analysis is to extract useful information from data and taking the decision based upon the data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Advisory</title>
      <link>www.example.com/services/business-advisory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/services/business-advisory/</guid>
      <description>We as the best business advisers analyse problems and potential risks businesses are facing and help provide advice. Clients have an opportunity to become technology advisers, as well as business advisers. This sector gives you the opportunity to work within accountancy firms of all sizes and across many industries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
